# Sadjy SADJAN

### SENIOR CLOUD INFRASTRUCTURE ENGINEER / DEVOPS ENGINEER

sadjy.sadjan@protonmail.com - linkedin.com/in/sadjy-sadjan-203449a0 - github.com/sadjy - gitlab.com/sadjy

Spent 9 years developing the skills to increase reliability, and performance of infrastructures. Hands-on expertise with Cloud Infrastructure platforms and Infrastructure-as-code, helping organizations instill infrastructure for the modern age.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Ancillabs Now

#### FOUNDER & LEAD CONSULTANT

- Provide expert DevOps and MLOps consulting services, helping clients enhance operational efficiency, reduce manual processes and implement scalable solutions.

# Star Atlas Dec. 2021 - Feb. 2024

#### PRINCIPAL INFRASTRUCTURE ENGINEER

- Initiated and conducted the entire migration to infrastructure-as-code (Terraform).

- Built up CI/CD environment dynamic agents, automated deployments, staged workflows.
- Improved Cloud services performance and reliability.
- Managed relationships with various RPC providers (coordinated updates)
- Migrated Hashicorp Vault environment to Cloud.
- Tightened security and user access management throughout multiple layers of the environments.
- Managed the Infrastructure team.

# IOTA Foundation Jul. 2018 – Nov. 2021

#### SYSOPS/SECOPS ENGINEER

- Rewrote the entire Ansible directory; Wrote 10+ new Ansible roles for broader automated configuration management.
- Actively participated in CI environment migration from Jenkins to Buildkite, and from Buildkite to Github Actions.
- Improved CI/CD lifecycle by implementing automated deployments (Ansible runs), ephemeral CI agents and security.
- Collaborated with IOTA core developers and management to ensure reliable operation of systems and provided support to Crypto exchanges.
- Designed and performed server and security audits, system backup procedures, and other recovery processes.
- Designed, deployed and maintained a data store cluster (scylla-db).

# Amaris Oct. 2016 - May. 2018

#### NETWORK AND SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

- T1, T2 and T3 support on LAN and WAN related issues,
- Multi-site worldwide Network infrastructure administration and operation,

- Data Center firewalls administration,
- Large-scale project management.

# CAPFI 6eme Sens Sep. 2015 – Sep. 2016

#### NETWORK AND SECURITY CONSULTANT

Mission - STET, La Défense (Paris):

- Defensive network security in a production environment,
- High-end support (T2 and T3) on a State classified vital importance infrastructure,
- Thorough project management on critical Networking datacenter,
- Technical and structured documentation redactions.

# Tata Consultancy Services Mar. 2015 – Aug. 2015

### SYSTEM AND NETWORK INTEGRATOR (internship)

### DevOps for a Java development team:

- Web and application server migration management and deployment,
- LSS on multiple development subsystems,
- Technical and educational redactions on these integration tasks and projects.

### SWIFT integration – consulting:

- T1 and T2 support on a SWIFT infrastructure,
- Installation, update, back-up and migration management of SWIFT technologies.

# **TLV Studios**Jun. 2014 – Oct. 2014

# IT OPERATOR (internship)

- Installation, configuration and perimeter probing for Wi-Fi access points,
- T1, T2 and T3 technical IT support on Digital Signage systems,
- Bash scripting and Linux systems configurations,
- Customer relationship management.

#### SKILLS

Technical:	<ul> <li>Unix (Kali, Debian, Arch)</li> <li>Networking</li> <li>GCP, AWS, Microsoft         Azure</li> <li>CI/CD (Buildkite, Github         Actions)</li> <li>HashiCorp Suite         (Terraform, Vault,         Nomad, Packer)</li> <li>IaC (OpenTofu,         Terraform,         CloudFormation)</li> </ul>	- Rust - OWASP Top 10 - Penetration Testing - Offsec - Burp Suite Pro - Metasploit - Bash - Python - Golang - JavaScript
Languages:	- French - Native - English - Bilingual	- Creole – Native - Korean – Intermediate

#### **EDUCATION**

**EFREI Engineering** 

School 2013 - 2015 NETWORKING & SERVICES, MASTER CYCLE MASTERS DEGREE / ENGINEERING DEGREE

Baimbridge High School

2010 - 2012

PREPARATORY SCHOOL IN ADVANCED MATHEMATICS

MPSI/MP

#### **COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS**

Deeplearning.ai -Coursera

Jun. 2019

SEQUENCE MODELS

Grade Achieved: 100.0%

Deeplearning.ai - Coursera

Jun. 2019

CONVOLUTIONAL NEURAL NETWORKS

Grade Achieved: 100.0%

Pentester Lab

Apr. 2019

TRAINING LAB

pentesterlab.com/profile/Sadi

Deeplearning.ai -Coursera

Jan. 2019

STRUCTURE MACHINE LEARNING PROJECTS

Grade Achieved: 100.0%

Deeplearning.ai -Coursera

Oct. 2018

IMPROVING DEEP NEURAL NETWORKS: HYPERPARAMETER TUNING,

REGULARIZATION AND OPTIMIZATION

Grade Achieved: 100.0%

Deeplearning.ai -Coursera

Aug. 2018

NEURAL NETWORKS AND DEEP LEARNING

Grade Achieved: 100.0%

Offensive Security

May. 2018

CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL (OSCP)

Penetration Testing with Kali Linux (PWK)

Paul Ekman Group

Dec. 2016

**CERTIFICATES OF TRAINING:** 

Micro Expressions: Expert Level Subtle Expressions: Expert Level Paul Ekman International

Nov. 2016

INTERNATIONAL CERTIFICATE IN EMOTIONAL SKILLS AND

COMPETENCIES

With distinction – Delivered by Success Management

English 2014 TOEIC: LISTENING AND READING

Score 910/990

# HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Social Engineering Psychology/Sociology Penetration Testing CFD Trading

Dance Teamplay-oriented video games Travel